we now have the the team from the top a
municipal Zhongshan girls high school in
taiwan who achieved also the meritorious
award achievement award so can we have
that the Taiwan team please
[Music]
yeah yeah
yo Mike
[Music]
Oh
don't shoot
[Music]
Chinchin
well
[Music]
the Venus
boo
Oh son Jack
well I
[Music]
we're from typing the new supporting
science this is the introduction and the
setting where that data from Taiwan we
considered objective factors and
personal preferences and I divided our
report into a three part first we find
the mortality rate second we took a lot
of foreign factors into consideration
that we can establish our model from
five different factors alas we mark a
simulation to make it clear question one
develop a model that uses mortality to
measure the quality of a hospital we
take advantage of these three data to
infer an expanded total mortality rate
after medical treatment because their
mortality can be totally different to
two adults variants we calculate all the
data for a to gender instead of C and we
simply these three factors on the
PowerPoint this is a demonstration of
our calculation F is female M is male we
try to we try to find a desktop after
medical treatment but those that are
confidential in Taiwan's so we automated
and that's what you can see on these two
pages
we just divided the number of patients
of emergency and outpatient clinic pilot
justo after medical treatment and we can
get hotel-motel arrays after medical
treatment we take the Delta of 2016 16
for example in this chart e equals to P
times R so it's clear to see how we
infer in the total mortality rate after
medical treatment after our calculation
oh no after our calculation we can get
em for the to gender we can see Donna
and further to gender normal
distribution we divide the results into
a six intervals instead of mortality
mortality scores this is females
this is nails we conclude them in this
chart the second question is about
measuring the quality of hospitals based
on more factors we found information
about the reason why people choose
hospitals then we chose for these
factors which is more objective to
create our model the first one is the
doctor score we found information about
top doctors from Businessweek magazine
we calculate the number of we calculate
a number of each division of top doctors
in each division of every hospital and
standardized M as X and transform X to a
distribution from one to six point nine
ninety a linear function to get why use
integral functions together final
doctoral score and take cardiology of
hospital one for example use the wave
above we can even get two points and two
is the is the dr. score of cardiology of
hospital one the next one is the
hospital score we measure the size and
resources of hospitals by the number of
pets referring to the information of
hospital evaluation we divided into six
intervals the third one is the
recommendation score we divided into two
parts if the patient received
recommendation and get one point if not
get zero the last one is the traffic
score it is matter about driving time to
the hospital last driving time implies
higher Travis score and last alderman
tilt his score from cousin one now we
can get a final final score of each
hospital to get the final score we need
to assemble a number for each bottle and
to do that would write a questionnaire
for patients to survey how important is
extractor each row represents each row
represents of factor we considered which
we just mentioned in the previous part
and each column represents a level of
importance and we use zero and one to
stand for whether the patient check or
not in this example the patient I care
about the equipment and care a lot about
doctors expertise and mrs. R factor
importance metrics we calculate the
factor important score by multiplying
the score each level of the Cent's the
sum of each row is one because each
because patients should choose only one
option in each row and this is an
example of the factor importance for
apparently calculated
then we can gather the function of each
factor analyst and a sum up dot
revolutionist one after we got the
propulsion of each factor I thought it
calculate the final score for each
Hospital and each row represents a
hospital and each ball one represents
the score of different factors in each
Hospital because III thus the score AI
three is different from the others so we
use our relation matrix to transform
auto score into the same level and after
that we can get the final spot so now as
per our case Malaysian sorry this is mr.
hello and he has heart disease he wants
to go to see the cardiologist but how
can you find hospitals which fit tip so
we will give him our user-friendly memo
okay but how can he use it
step one has to write down his name and
his gender the division he wants to go
the address and check the form whether
it has received the recommendation the
most important part is filled in the
fourth we have five factors and five
fours on our words and with one as to
not quite at all and with five o'clock
the higher the score is the greater the
degree is and each row is required so I
can finish the formed and she just click
the Android and the nor information that
he can get our invoice with perhaps
became three to five hospitals for
reference and advantage of our memo is
that it's easy handy and convenient is
also Baraga in the future if I have
chance to get more data we can expand
our model or give more precise results
to our users
and this is the calculation behind our
model
[Music]